(Things I Like)
Nice to see you all.
An impressive guest will be joining us today.
To celebrate 2026, the Year of the Red Horse,
- we launched a special project, - Yes.
Rainbow Running Horses.
She's the only elite chef in Korea...
who has worked in 1, 2, and 3-Michelin starred restaurants.
Then when she starred on "Culinary Class Wars 2,"
she left a strong impression with this gesture, "Roar."
Kim Si Hyeon, also known as Little Tiger, please come on out.
(The cute scene-stealer from "Culinary Class Wars 2")
(When she made a vegetable dish which was her signature dish, )
(she demonstrated impressive skills and left an impression.)
(She has experience working...)
(in 1, 2, and 3-Michelin starred restaurants.)
(The charismatic chef with an unexpected charm, Kim Si Hyeon)
(Shy)
- "Roar." - Hello.
- Please stand in the center. - This is surreal.
- Nice to meet you. - Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - Introduce yourself to our viewers.
Hello. I was...
(Nervous)
I was on "Culinary Class Wars 2."
My name is Kim Si Hyeon and my nickname was Little Tiger.
This is so surreal. Is there a reason you were cast...
for Rainbow Running Horses?
- Horse isn't my zodiac sign. - Right.
But I'd love to give this year a good run.
- That's right. - Yes. That's why I'm here.
- With that logic, - Yes.
- anyone can join our show. - Gosh, no.
Some people don't want to gallop hard like horses.
Some might want to trot.
(Some might want to trot.)
Tell us how it feels to be on our show.
- I'm a huge fan of the show. - Yes.
So this feels so surreal now.
- Really? - Yes.
I can't believe that I'll be a Rainbow Club member.
- You're a member now. - Yes. My gosh.
- I'm really excited and nervous. - Yes.
- There are so many things to do. - I'll do my best.
Not only did Si Hyeon's dish go viral,
but her pose also went viral.
Could you show us the original version?
- Oh, my. - My gosh.
I can't believe I'll see it in person.
- Right. - "Roar."
- Show us. - Please show us.
- Oh, no. - What's your nickname?
It's Little Tiger.
- What? Little? - Little...
Tiger.
(Little Tiger)
- My gosh. - I love it.
- No, I love it. - Oh, my.
- No. - It's great.
I'm so embarrassed.
She's the third star of Rainbow Running Horses.
Little Tiger is galloping hard like a horse this year.
Si Hyeon will share her day-to-day life...
for the first time on TV.
Let's check it out together.
(Roar)
(The Year of the Red Horse)
(Rainbow Running Horses, Part 3)
(Little Tiger Is on the Hunt, Roar!)
"Roar."
(Little Tiger Si Hyeon is still fast asleep in the morning.)
Her room looks clean.
I feel too shy to watch myself.
(Shy)
(She turns off the alarm right away.)
(Getting up)
Hello. I've been living alone for seven years.
I'm Chef Kim Si Hyeon and my nickname is Little Tiger.
(Roar!)
- She's so adorable. - How cute.
- What year were you born? - I was born in 2000.
You've been living alone for seven years,
so does it mean you've been on your own since high school?
Right. I started working in 12th grade...
- Yes. - since my winter break.
- You started at a young age. - I've been living alone since then.
How does someone so young get a job...
at fine dining restaurants like three-Michelin starred restaurants?
Did you have to take a test? How does that go?
I got a job as soon as I graduated from high school.
So I didn't have any work experience.
I put together a portfolio to show all of my cooking experience.
- Like winning an award and so on? - Yes. Something like that.
But didn't you graduate from a prestigious high school?
Right. I graduated from Korea Culinary Arts Science High School.
- It's a specialized high school. - Right.
She was already on track...
- to be an elite chef. - Yes, she was.
But graduating from that school didn't guarantee a job...
- at Michelin starred restaurants. - Right.
She put together a portfolio and submitted it...
- during interviews. - Right. I also included a letter.
(But hold on.)
Everyone had a lot of questions.
She hasn't even woken up yet in the clip.
We don't know much...
- about the culinary world. - Right.
(Si Hyeon finally wakes up.)
(Current time, 7:10am)
- She's so diligent. - Why does she wake up so early?
I feel too shy to watch it.
(Getting up)
(She busily makes the bed first.)
She's very neat. It must be because she's a chef. You're so neat.
My gosh.
(Turning off the light in the bedroom)
(Turning on the light in the living room)
(Let us introduce Si Hyeon's house.)
My gosh. Oh, my.
It's super clean.
Her house looks neat and clean.
Her pantry is in the living room.
(Her bedroom is minimalistic.)
It's been less than a month since I moved in.
I don't have my own kitchen.
So I thought it'd be nice...
to move into a house I could also use as my studio.
That's why I decided to move into a house with a big kitchen.
(She settled on a house with a big kitchen.)
(The kitchen is full of her cooking tools.)
(Ingredients are neatly divided.)
- How neat. - Look at how they're divided.
This is an important part of my house.
I need a lot of cooking tools and equipment,
so I needed enough space to store all of them.
(Dishware fills up the massive pantry.)
- You have so many pretty dishes. - Dishes.
You have a pantry...
- where most people have a TV. - Right.
I also have a lot of appliances.
I have a vacuum sealer,
an ice cream machine, a food dehydrator,
a blender, and a sous vide machine.
A pasta maker.
- You have all of these. - I have that.
I've been buying them over these seven years.
So I ended up with a lot of equipment.
The whole rack is like my treasure box.
(She walks past her treasure box...)
(and goes to the bathroom.)
- Oh, no! - Why?
- You look the same. - Well...
- Considering everything, - Yes.
- you look great. - Really?
There isn't a single embarrassing moment.
You should watch one of my episodes.
Oh, my.
(You'll feel very relieved.)
(Checking her perfectly-fine appearance)
(Let's see.)
(Rattling)
(She starts cutting her nails.)
She's cutting her nails in the morning.
It's my habit to check my nails before washing my face.
When you have long fingernails,
you sometimes end up chopping off your fingernails.
Or your fingernails could end up in food.
I ended up fixating on having short fingernails.
"My fingernails must be short."
(She cuts her fingernails before washing her face as usual.)
(Short)
(Then she brushes her teeth...)
(and washes her face.)
(Refreshed)
(Giggling)
(She quietly sits next to Wilson.)
This is crazy.
(Let me take a picture with him.)
(Making a V)
- I couldn't believe it. - You look like a kid.
She looks so young.
(Smiling)
(After taking a picture with Wilson, )
(she goes straight to the fridge.)
I'm curious...
- about what she has in her fridge. - Right, exactly.
(Her fridge is neatly organized.)
- Gosh, her fridge too? - That's her fridge.
It's well-organized.
She labeled everything in the fridge.
(She thoroughly put on labels.)
(There's also food she pickled herself.)
- You also have long-lasting food. - She wrote down the dates.
- She included dates in the labels. - I see. So...
I have to let them age for a specific number of days.
Personally, I find food...
like marmalades, pickles, and kimchi...
that require fermentation and aging processes fascinating.
So I like storing food before I consume it.
(She's aging seasonal food all over her house.)
(Opening up the vegetable basket)
(I'll go with you, shepherd's purse.)
- Shepherd's purse is in season. - Shepherd's purse is amazing.
(She turns on the light in the kitchen first.)
(She starts cooking in earnest.)
I'm so curious about her breakfast.
(She puts a pot of water on the stove.)
(She prepares all kinds of seasoning like chili powder and doenjang.)
(Let's start cooking.)
I think her gaze changed a bit.
(Putting on a fierce gaze like Little Tiger)
- She's tying up her hair. - Like that?
That means business.
(It's time for Little Tiger to reveal her claws.)
(Aiming at her target)
(Washing)
(Wash the shepherd's purse in cold water.)
Gosh, shepherd's purse looks good.
- It's great in doenjang soup. - Right.
I love shepherd's purse.
(Her hunt on shepherd's purse is going smoothly.)
(Rustling)
(She brings out a bag of ramyeon.)
- What? - What?
I love ramyeon.
(Giggling)
I tried cooking with different brands of ramyeon.
I also tried different recipes to cook ramyeon.
I had some leftover shepherd's purse from yesterday.
So I made doenjang ramyeon with shepherd's purse.
My gosh. You ate ramyeon for breakfast?
I thought you'd make stew.
- Right. Like doenjang ramyeon. - Exactly.
I'm curious about the pairing of ramyeon and shepherd's purse.
Shepherd's purse ramyeon?
It's just like cooking ramyeon. I added the seasoning packet.
(She starts by adding the seasoning packet.)
Then I added a tablespoon of doenjang of my choice.
You're adding doenjang to the ramyeon.
(Then she adds the noodles to the doenjang broth.)
- I love that brand of ramyeon. - Right? That's tasty.
If I'm craving something spicy,
- I'd use the spicy ramyeon. - The spicy ramyeon.
But since I was having it for breakfast,
I wanted to be able to taste shepherd's purse and doenjang.
So I went with the potato noodles.
(She chose the ramyeon with potato noodles.)
(Adding chili powder)
When the noodles are about cooked,
add chopped shepherd's purse.
It's a restaurant dish.
(Grabbing)
I need to add a bit of the fish sauce at the end.
(The last ingredient is a bit of the anchovy fish sauce.)
(Fish sauce?)
You're adding anchovy fish sauce?
Anchovy fish sauce?
That looks tasty.
(It's all ready.)
- It was really good. - That does look good.
- Many people will try this recipe. - Totally.
(Her doenjang ramyeon with shepherd's purse is ready.)
(Pulling)
(Steaming)
(Taking a big bite)
- She's eating with gusto. - Gosh, that sounds appetizing.
(Satisfied)
(She only eats the shepherd's purse this time.)
(Oh, right.)
(She watches a dating show during her meal.)
A dating show.
(Smiling)
This is crazy.
(While her eyes are fixed on her phone, )
(she inhales the noodles nonstop.)
(She picks up a chopstickful of shepherd's purse.)
(The fragrant aroma spreads in her mouth.)
How does shepherd's purse taste?
- It's slightly bitter. - Bitter?
Here's the thing. It's cold right now.
As for shepherd's purse from winter,
it holds onto a lot of sugar...
- not to freeze underground. - Right.
- So it's sweeter when it's cooked. - I see.
- It's actually sweet. - It's packed with nutrients.
Underground winter vegetables like spring cabbages,
shepherd's purse, spinach, and winter spinach...
- are all tasty. - They're all sweet.
- Right. - No way.
- They hold onto sugars underground. - Then...
After hearing your explanation,
I'd love to have some vegetables even when I'm not a fan of them.
- Really? - Yes.
- I should buy it right away. - I'll go and buy some.
- I'll buy it right away. - I should go and buy it.
(She drinks it up from the pot while smelling the aroma.)
(That was a good meal.)
(Empty)
- She eats a lot. - She really does.
(She lets down her hair since she's done with her hunt.)
(Splashing)
(She washes the dishes as soon as she's done eating.)
I love that you're so clean and neat.
(Tying her hair)
(She ties up her hair again.)
(It hasn't even been 8am yet.)
(Lifting)
- Is that a stone cutting board? - She's taking out a cutting board.
- It looks like she'll cook again. - She looks so professional.
You're very different...
- with your hair up. - Right.
My chef side is on now.
- What? - Hallabong?
What are those? They're huge.
- They're so big. - They look like hallabong.
- They're hallabong. - Really?
(She had bought a bunch of massive-sized fruit.)
(Her sink is full now.)
You can only have them now.
They're called daeng yuzu.
- It's a native variety of yuzu. - Yuzu.
It's grown here.
- That's as big as my face. - Seriously.
- You can even roll it. - Right.
It's huge.
- I've never seen daeng yuzu before. - It's so big.
(Fascinated)
(She also cleans the bowl.)
(Spraying)
(She rubs alcohol disinfectant on the bowl.)
(Grabbing)
(Chopping)
(Skillfully preparing daeng yuzu)
(Focused)
The peels are thick.
- That looks good. - Right.
(Separating fruit flesh and peels without hesitation)
I'm going to make daeng yuzu marmalade today.
She's making a marmalade.
As it's an unfamiliar marmalade to everyone,
daeng yuzu is hard to come by.
The first time I tasted it, I thought it tasted amazing.
I was so sad that I didn't have enough...
to make marmalades for next year.
I didn't want the next-year me to feel sad.
So I've been making it every year.
It's your secret weapon.
(Chopping them nonstop to make the marmalade)
- You're left-handed. - Yes, I am.
Lefties look cool for some reason.
(She cleans the cutting board right after using it.)
(She grabs her knife again right after separating the flesh.)
Wait, do people eat that part too?
(What's that?)
(She carves out a thin strip of the peel.)
(Delicate)
It's crazy that she can make it as thin as that.
The white part is a bit bitter.
- There's bitterness to it. Yes. - Just like tangerines.
- Like tangerines. - Yes.
So I remove the white part...
- and leave only the zest on. - That must be...
- So you're using the zest. - Yes.
That's so fascinating. Look at her slicing that out.
(The fruit is getting separated into three different layers.)
(Feeling tired)
(Her wrist aches from constant slicing.)
Her wrist must hurt.
(Stopping)
(She suddenly stops cutting.)
(She washes her hand and comes back.)
The entire process is clean and neat.
- Even the alignment of the zest. - I love that.
(She makes coffee.)
(Slicing the zest)
(Twisting)
That's yuzu coffee.
(She coats the rim of her coffee cup with the daeng yuzu zest.)
(This hits the spot.)
You might've seen it at cocktail bars.
The part of the glass where your lips touch...
is called the rim.
When you twist a thin slice of the zest...
on the rim,
the oily layer of the fruit pops...
and gives a nice citrusy fragrance.
So since I was prepping daeng yuzu, I thought about trying that out.
So I did. And it smelled so fresh.
(She resumes after recharging on caffeine.)
(Focused)
(Julienning the yuzu with swift wrist movements)
- That's the amazing knife skill... - Right.
Chef Kim Hee Eun approved of.
"Amazing."
That's really hard.
(She keeps on chopping.)
(Making a pile of yuzu strips in consistent thickness)
(Her hand movements are machine-like.)
(Impressed)
All done.
She cut everything?
They look like chips.
They do.
(It took 1 hour and 30 minutes to prepare the ingredient.)
(Whirring)
(Pouring the blended flesh over a strainer)
Without that process,
the marmalade gets too pulpy.
- So I run it through a strainer. - She'll use that for the marmalade.
- I see. - Yes.
(She combines the zest and juice.)
It's sugar.
(Adding sugar in an equal amount)
(Stirring)
- That looks great. - Look at the color.
How do you usually eat that?
Do you make tea with it?
You can make tea with it.
Or you can add it to sparkling water.
- Sparkling water? - Yes, that's one way to eat it.
- You can add it to peanut porridge. - Yes.
Sometimes, I use it instead of plum syrup.
You can replace sugar...
- with it. - Right.
(All she has to do now is wait for it to age.)
(Be tasty.)
- You have to let it age for a year? - Right.
- I let it age for over a year. - My gosh.
I now see that giving marmalade as a present...
- was something truly special. - Of course.
- It requires a lot of attention. - I also...
You must feel proud that you made it.
Right. I felt great.
(Her kitchen is spotless too.)
(She goes to the bathroom after finishing a long task.)
(Touching)
(A sharp inhale)
I don't need to wash my hair.
Oh, no.
It's okay. I don't wash up often either.
It's a hassle to wash hair when it's long.
I usually wash my hair at night...
because of the oil from food.
- So I wash it at night. - Right.
Then I check how my hair looks in the morning.
(Thoroughly dabbing on her face)
(Wearing her hair down)
She's letting her hair down.
(Putting on a jacket)
She's going out.
(She gets ready to go out in an instant.)
(Turning off the light)
(Opening up)
(She takes out a cart from the shoe closet.)
That must be her grocery cart.
- Don't moms always carry one? - Right.
(There's one more?)
This is too hard.
(The bag that matches today's outfit is...)
What's the dilemma? Your fashion?
(Finding her adorable)
(The cute dotted cart is chosen.)
I guess she factors that into her outfit.
She must try to match it to her outfit.
"Which one should I pick..."
"for today's look?"
I've never seen anyone think that long about grocery carts.
(Si Hyeon comes out with the dotted grocery cart.)
- How cute. - It looks like...
- her mom sent her out on an errand. - Yes.
"Buy a block of tofu."
"Okay."
(Running to finish her errand)
(She runs until she's out of breath.)
Where's she going?
(Where is she going?)
The bus stop.
(She sits on the bench at a bus stop.)
(Spotting)
(The bus arrives just in time.)
Do you not drive?
I don't have a driver's license.
- I take the bus. - Taking the bus is...
the most convenient in Seoul.
Right.
(She freely heads to her destination on a bus.)
That's the perk of taking the bus.
I guess there's a specific place you want to go to.
Right. I go there often.
(Getting up)
(Si Hyeon gets off at her regular spot.)
I've arrived at Gyeongdong Market.
You went to Gyeongdong Market.
(It stretches out right next to the bus stop.)
I've been coming to Gyeongdong Market for a very long time.
- I think it's the biggest market. - It is.
One wrong turn, and you get lost.
- It's that big. - Right.
(Si Hyeon's hunting ground is filled with ingredients.)
"Hunting ground."
The market always has fresh ingredients.
So I go there more often.
(Si Hyeon is roaming the market to look for her prey.)
(Smoothly squeezing through the crowd)
It's so crowded today.
(She stops in front of a crowded stall.)
- Hello. - Here you go.
(It's impossible to skip on twisted donuts at markets.)
They're so good.
The twisted donuts are the best at markets.
- My gosh. - Goodness.
I didn't want my sugar to crash.
So I went to the twisted donut stall first.
She knows what's up.
- Eating it fresh is important. - Right.
- You must eat it right away. - Here you go.
Thank you. Have a good day.
You know your stuff.
- You kept the bag open. - Of course.
If you close up the bag, the donuts get soggy.
I did that once.
And my friend criticized me for it big time.
- I'd defriend you right away. - Hey.
- You really shouldn't do that. - I should cut ties with you.
- The cold air was going into it. - Gosh. What are you talking about?
If you close up the bag...
- Dear me. - Gosh.
I got scolded again.
(Taking a bite before it gets soggy)
- Gosh, that looks good. - Oh, my.
(Humming)
(A big bite of the twisted donut...)
(puts her in a good mood.)
She looks happy.
(Taking a bite even at the chaotic market)
(Wiping her fingers on her pants)
(Glancing)
(She starts walking around the market in earnest.)
- Hello. - I'm curious about...
what you'll buy there.
- Hello. - Hello.
- They look great. - Here.
(A stall with a lot of greenery catches her eye.)
I go to this vegetable stall regularly.
They look great. Oh, my.
There are so many ingredients you can buy...
now that I'm looking at them at once.
And the prices are so reasonable.
Overseas, people cook with herbs.
In Korea, we have our greens.
Their fragrances are all different.
And we have to handle them differently too.
To me, this is like a department store.
I love greens.
I watched your episode.
Hello.
I bought some for you when I bought mine.
- I got you twisted donuts. - That was good of you.
- They're good. - Aren't you guys...
- already close? - We are.
(Let me hunt down some greens.)
- Two bundles of spring cabbages. - Okay.
I'll take those today.
(Picking the spring cabbages without hesitation)
Spring cabbages are so good.
They look so tasty.
I'll take the island spinach. Not the cleaned ones.
- Sure. The ones with dirt. - Island spinach?
It's a type of spinach.
- Give me ones with a lot of roots. - This one is thick. Sure.
How much do you want?
I just need about 375g of it.
- This? - This looks good.
- Do you want it? - Yes.
The roots are tiny. Are you okay with that?
- That looks great. - Sure.
Island spinach is really tasty right now.
When you look at the roots,
some of them are pink and thick.
Those are the tasty ones.
I recommend blanching them with the roots.
What's the difference between island spinach and regular spinach?
Regular spinach has straight stems.
So it's just fragrant.
But island spinach was grown...
- with a lot of sea breezes. - It's just like the name.
- So it's called island spinach. - Right.
- Really? - Island spinach grows closely...
to the ground and spreads out.
So the leaves are thicker and sweeter.
That's how they're different.
I want siler divaricata...
and coastal siler.
- I want 200g each. - You want 200g each.
Young sprouts of siler divaricata...
are in season now.
They're not chewy or bitter.
If you pickle them right now,
you can enjoy soft siler divaricata for a long time.
So I love it.
- I'd love to try some. - Same here.
Your explanations about greens are so interesting.
- Really? - She's the Greens Master.
What Chef Anh Sung Jae said about you went viral.
"I love that there's a young chef who loves greens."
- Right. - Same here. I was grateful...
- that you were on the show. - It's rare.
- Young people don't like greens. - You like them as you get older.
I really wanted...
- Right? I bet. - to hear that from him.
You don't have mugwort yet, right?
No. Mugwort is taking a while to be prepared.
It's been snowing.
- It snowed on the field. Yes. - Because it's cold?
I need to wait a little longer to buy henbit, right?
Right. It's not available now.
When I was young, I loved henbit flowers.
Those flowers are also edible.
Fatsia shoot looks great.
I bet she wants to buy everything.
It's impossible to stay calm at vegetable stalls.
I'll take one.
I wasn't going to buy fatsia shoot.
It looks so fresh.
- This one. - Gosh, it looks great.
This is crazy.
Silver wild chives don't have long leaves.
- Right. - How do you usually eat them?
They're good when they're stir-fried.
You can eat them like you eat small onions.
They're quite tasty.
- I'll take canola greens. - Canola greens.
I'll take 300g of it.
- I'll take 200g of garlic chives. - Just 200g?
I'll also take 100g of brachycarpa.
- You also want brachycarpa. - They're all in season now.
(Hold on a second.)
How do you usually eat barley grass?
Barley grass...
- Are they barley sprouts? - Yes.
(Barley grass)
Many people add it to the fermented skate liver soup.
People in the lower regions do that. People also add it...
- to the kimchi or doenjang soup. - Fermented skate.
If it's tender, you can season it and eat it.
- Please give me 200g of it... - Okay.
I can season and eat.
You plan what to do as you buy the ingredients.
That's right.
How cool. It's my first time cooking barley grass.
(Excited)
Although you cook often,
you can still find new edible greens.
I know. I find it fascinating too.
- That's all. - Is that all?
(Please calculate the total including the barley grass.)
- It's 71 dollars. - Did she say 71 dollars?
About 70 dollars' worth of greens?
- About 70 dollars' worth of greens? - I have just the right amount.
(She pays in cash.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Her bag gets filled with greens.)
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Make tasty dishes.
- Have a nice day. - Okay. Thank you.
It must feel very nice.
- It makes me the happiest. - Exactly.
Chamsongi mushrooms, please.
How about five dollars' worth?
You must look so cute to her.
- Please give me the hard ones. - Okay.
- Hello. - Hello.
Please give me two dollars' worth...
- of green garlic. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Okay. Bye.
- Have a nice day. - Okay.
The greens will become popular.
- Seriously. They'll become popular. - Seriously.
They'll become popular.
(She goes outside the market after purchasing many items.)
What's your favorite kind of greens?
- My favorite? - Let's say you have to pick one.
- It's a difficult question. - I'm curious.
It'll be hard since she likes so many kinds.
You can blanch them and season them,
make fresh kimchi, or add them in soup.
I like different kinds for different cooking styles.
- Of course. - But if I must choose one...
(Which kind of greens is Greens Master's favorite?)
Daylily leaves.
- Daylily leaves? - I love daylily leaves.
What are those?
- Daylily leaves. - I know what they are.
- They look like spinach. - They're flat.
That's right. Once they're blanched, they're very tender...
and sweet.
They're very tasty.
(She comes back home with her hands heavy.)
Her hands are heavy.
(Rummaging)
(She puts the greens on the kitchen counter.)
You tied your hair.
- It means that you'll cook. - It means that I'll cook.
(She puts on an apron, her battle clothing.)
(She picks up a bag of greens.)
(Sniffing)
It was my first time cooking it.
- Barley grass. - Yes.
(She rinses it thoroughly.)
(She adds bay salt to the boiling water.)
- She began to experiment. - Yes.
I decided to test different methods.
(How will I cook it in a fun way?)
(She blanches the barley grass first.)
You try it as it is.
- Does it taste bad? - What's that facial expression?
- She doesn't like it. - She doesn't like it.
Let me boil it a bit more.
(She blanches the barley grass a bit more in the hot saltwater.)
(Slurping)
(Perhaps it'll taste good if I rinse it with cold water.)
None of the methods worked.
(I see.)
You tried different methods.
This test was a failure.
It came out too tough.
How did it become tough when you blanched it?
Isn't the taste similar...
- no matter the texture? - It's totally different.
- I see. - How does the barley grass taste?
Is it sweet?
It tastes like chive without the bite.
It tastes like savory chive.
(Fascinated)
I thought about how to improve the tough texture.
- Texture? - I'll stir-fry it...
and fry it in the future.
(Barley grass test: The texture is tough.)
(She makes notes as soon as the test ends.)
You make notes.
- That way... - It's your fortune.
It'll be a shame to use other people's recipes only.
So I try different cooking methods...
to find the right one.
You write down all sorts of things.
Do you study different cooking methods...
- on a regular basis? - That's right.
- That's impressive. - You continue to do that.
- I got chills. - Really?
(I got chills.)
I keep simple ham recipes...
on my phone.
- Really? - I'm serious.
(Chills)
- It's an act of creation. - Exactly.
You're right.
(After the creation exercise, she goes back into the kitchen.)
(She pours something into the bowl.)
Short-necked clams. They have a refreshing taste.
(She prepares the short-necked clam.)
(She adds enough water and puts the pot over the fire.)
(She adds a bit of rice wine to eliminate the fishy smell.)
(I'll boil them like this.)
(Let's see.)
Green garlic. Perilla soft tofu.
Island spinach.
(Housewarming party)
Today, I'll invite friends over for a housewarming party.
I'll make dishes for the housewarming party.
Today's dinner consists...
of the pot rice using short-necked clams,
perilla soft tofu jjigae with blue crabs,
- and four kinds of greens. - That sounds delicious.
- Blue crabs and perilla. - Fresh spring cabbage...
and brachycarpa kimchi,
doenjang-seasoned island spinach,
seasoned canola greens,
- and green garlic... - Green garlic.
Dressed with red sauce.
When you go to a fine-dining place,
they explain each dish with that voice.
For island spinach,
I mixed tojang and regular doenjang...
you can get at a store for fragrance.
I seasoned canola greens with soy sauce, salt,
plum syrup,
- and sesame oil. - It looks delicious.
Then I seasoned green garlic with chili pepper.
The cooking method is different for each kind of greens.
Each one has different fragrance and flavors.
I don't add garlic.
- Garlic is overpowering. - Yes.
They look the same.
They aren't the same.
- It's difficult. - We don't know how they taste.
I think you'll live a long life.
Right? That's how you live...
- a long life. - You eat many healthy foods.
(She stir-fries dried aster scaber with perilla oil in the pot.)
It looks tasty.
(Then she pours the soaked rice over the stir-fried greens.)
Pot rice.
So that's how you make it.
(She mixes the greens and rice.)
Then I add the short-necked clam broth...
- to make the pot rice. - That substitutes the water.
(Once it boils, the pot rice will be ready.)
(Rattling)
(Blue crabs are next to the pot rice.)
(Let's see.)
(She harvests the scallions she has kept in a pot of soil.)
I didn't grow them.
- You planted them. - Yes.
- I bought them. - They grow more if you plant them.
- They keep growing. - They last for a long time.
- They don't go bad if I water them. - Really?
Perilla soft tofu jjigae...
is my favorite dish from the sauna I visit often.
I decided to make a similar dish today.
I put blue crabs at the bottom of the earthen pot.
I topped them with onions, scallions,
enoki mushrooms, and Cheongyang peppers.
Then I added about four spoons of ground perilla seeds.
- You like ground perilla seeds. - That's right. I love it.
- It'll eliminate the fishy smell. - That's right.
And I added a bit of doenjang since it goes well with blue crabs.
(Let's see if the pot rice came out well.)
It looks so tasty.
(Look how glossy it is.)
(We're so jealous.)
- That's insane. - The chef's dishes...
- look delicious. - She sure is different.
(That's the taste I want.)
(The perilla soft tofu jjigae begins to boil.)
It looks delicious.
(The seasoning is perfect.)
(She completes the dish by topping it with soft tofu.)
(Happy to see her friends, she hurriedly goes to the door.)
What? The three of you came together.
We met near the house.
- Something smells delicious. - What kind of friends are they?
- Seriously. - Who are they?
- Take this. - The coats...
- What is it? - There's ice cream inside.
- Ice cream? - It's a present.
- They're her actual friends. - What?
Nice place. What's this?
(What's up with the kitchen?)
- "What's this?" - It's a party.
It smells incredible.
They're my friends from the neighborhood.
We meet up once or more in a month...
to relieve our stress...
and eat together.
Firstly, there's my best friend...
from Korea Culinary Arts Science High School, Lee So Yeon.
So Yeon is in charge of desserts...
- at the L brand's restaurant. - Really?
- What's the L brand's restaurant? - Desserts.
Louis Vuitton.
Louis Vuitton?
Hyun Woo is a junior from the same high school...
by one year.
He currently cooks at a restaurant with wine pairing.
It's a one-star restaurant.
- Everyone is successful. - The third one...
is Moon Jong Hyun.
We worked together at my previous workplace.
I invited them over.
It's the chefs' gathering.
What are these plates?
It looks like you got more.
(Her chef friends begin to help out wordlessly.)
Since they're chefs as well, things will go fast when they help.
- Exactly. - They'll have good teamwork.
All of them are professionals.
That's right. The way they help is different.
(She had raw fish delivered earlier.)
- Raw fish. - She ordered raw fish.
Sea bream and yellowtail.
(Raw fish gets transferred to a plate prettily.)
I really tried to wrap up early.
- What? - I really tried to wrap up early.
I mean...
The seasoned greens look tasty.
- I made them with care. - All right.
(Si Hyeon and her friends set the table in an orderly way.)
It's hot.
- It looks tasty. - Let's eat.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you. - Everything looks tasty.
That's the best.
- Would you explain the menu? - All right.
Firstly, I ordered raw fish.
The presentation makes it very appetizing.
Seriously.
This is seasoned canola greens.
I seasoned canola greens with soup soy sauce.
The dish looks so glossy.
This is island spinach which is the tastiest right now.
I seasoned it with doenjang and perilla oil.
- It's so glossy. - This is green garlic.
I seasoned it with chili powder.
This is fresh spring cabbage and brachycarpa kimchi.
As for this one...
It's pot rice made with dried aster scaber.
- It looks tasty. - I can't believe...
she made it at home.
- Perilla soft tofu jjigae. - Soft tofu and pot rice...
- will go well together. - That jjigae looks tasty.
- Can we eat? I'm hungry. - Of course.
- Enjoy the food. - Thank you for the food.
The rice is a bit mushy.
- No, it isn't. - I like mushy rice.
The seasoning is perfect.
We always smell the food before eating.
- Chefs think about the flavors. - Yes.
- The island spinach is so sweet. - Right?
- Yes. - It's insane.
It's tasty.
(Don't mention it.)
I was craving seasoned greens.
The table suits the start of spring.
I shopped at the Gyeongdong Market.
Nice.
I haven't had such a healthy meal in a while.
- It happens when you live alone. - Yes.
- We're eating an expensive meal. - I know.
Enjoy the meal.
(He becomes absorbed in eating the expensive meal.)
They work at restaurants.
- It looks delicious. - That's nice.
(The chef friends are in love with Si Hyeon's seasoned greens.)
- I'm hungry. - That's one.
The crabs are tasty.
(Seeing her friends eat with gusto makes her smile brightly.)
(His mouth waters.)
Although I have a child's tastes,
- I really want to eat that meal. - Really?
Let's eat with the members sometime.
- The members. - The members.
I thought you might be curious about the taste,
so I prepared the food.
Nice!
- I had no expectations. - Nice!
Nice! Thank you.
I don't know what to do. I'm so nervous.
- Thank you. - This is the biggest table...
- we've gotten on the show. - Really?
- It's a big table. - I'm so nervous.
You brought so much food.
- The table looks so heavy. - Seriously.
- Is this the aster scaber rice? - That's right.
It's the dried aster scaber pot rice with the short-necked clam broth.
(4 kinds of green greens)
(You can dip the island spinach in makjang.)
I made it the day before.
- It's the dried laver jangajji. - My goodness.
- Dried laver jangajji. - I sprinkled perilla oil.
Dried laver jangajji is to die for.
This is dried aster scaber and this is fresh aster scaber.
- Fresh aster scaber. - It's from Hadong, Mount Jiri.
Since chamgsongi mushrooms were very tasty,
I seasoned them with aster scaber.
Thank you so much for cooking all these dishes.
- Don't mention. - Thank you for your hard work.
- Let's hurry up and eat. - I'm so nervous.
- Let's taste the dishes. - Don't be nervous.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for your hard work.
- It's a proper meal. - The amount is just right.
The amount is perfect.
(She tries the dried aster scaber pot rice first.)
Try the aster scaber rice.
Really?
- She really uses... - It's a hassle to cook these.
Different ingredients.
You know...
The seasoned aster scaber is savory.
It's tasty.
(They take a bite as they savor the fragrance.)
- Hey. - Hey, the spring cabbage is tasty.
- The aster scaber is so fragrant. - Right?
Thank goodness. I was very worried.
(It suits the tastes of CODE KUNST, the nibbler.)
It's in season.
- It's really tasty. - Right?
(Sniffing)
(Eating)
Gosh, you're good.
- It's no joke. - Seriously.
It's so tasty.
(It's so tasty.)
(Taking a big bite)
(This is it.)
- I mean... - Aster scaber is so fragrant.
What's this?
- It's so tasty. - Island spinach.
Island spinach.
I'm so happy.
(It suits the tastes of the young Dowoon as well.)
Try the dried laver jangajji.
I didn't know that you could make jangajji with it.
(Everyone enjoys Si Hyeon's food.)
Seriously, this is...
- It's fragrant, right? - Yes, it's insane.
I ate all the greens.
(There's a grain of rice on his chin.)
(He enjoys the fragrance of spring.)
It's the greens sushi.
(He wraps up the meal with the greens sushi.)
Little Tiger, you've survived.
Thank you.
It was the best.
(Roaring)
Seriously, it was insane.
- It was so nice. - You're too kind.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - I really enjoyed it.
- Thank you. - We fell in love with the greens.
- My mind feels clearer. - Right?
I'm so happy.
- Let's clear the table. - Okay.
Shall we eat rice cake and ice cream?
- Is there ice cream? - There's yogurt ice cream.
Even the dessert is perfect.
(Rice cake and ice cream sound nice, right?)
- I'll clean up as you prepare them. - That sounds good.
It's so nice that we can divide up the tasks when we meet up.
(As her friends clean up, )
(Si Hyeon takes out mysterious food.)
- Is that duteoptteok? - Yes.
(A few hours ago, Si Hyeon prepared the filling and rice cake.)
(She wrapped the filling with rice cake.)
This is the same as the Dubai chewy cookie, DCC.
I think it's the K-DCC...
that contains pine nuts and chestnuts.
K-DCC.
(K-DCC, duteoptteok)
- Did you make duteoptteok? - Yes.
It was So Yeon's birthday.
(The duteoptteok cake is complete.)
(Embarrassed)
(Happy birthday to you.)
- Thank you. - Happy birthday.
I haven't received rice cake...
- in a long while. - Really?
Will you make the dessert now?
Make a quenelle.
- Shall I scoop it out for everyone? - Yes.
(Pushing)
(Impressed)
It looks like a quail egg.
I know.
(The shape of the ice cream is extraordinary.)
- Why is it so funny? - It looks pretty.
- It's a bit. - It's pretty.
(Yogurt and daeng yuzu ice cream)
- She made it pretty with a spoon. - I know.
Louis Vuitton sure is different.
The shape is called a quenelle.
For people who make desserts,
it's a source of pride like the chefs' knife skills.
That's right.
- Thank you. - You made it well.
It looks nice, right? This one is the best.
(So Yeon made an incredibly pretty quenelle.)
It's tasty.
(She puts a spoonful of class into her mouth.)
I bought it.
I feel great.
I'll eat this.
(It looks tasty.)
How is it?
I like how the big grains with chestnut pieces provide texture.
(I'm glad that they're eating well.)
When I talk to them,
I learn so many new things.
The more I dig, the more I find new things.
It makes me go back...
to my initial enthusiasm.
With cabbage, you can make soup, kimchi,
seasoned vegetables, and jeon.
I want to be an all-rounder.
Shall I be Cabbage Guru?
(Laughing)
- The last glass. - The last glass.
- Thank you for the invitation. - Thank you for coming.
(The Journey of Little Tiger Who Is Still Eager to Learn)
We enjoyed the video.
I could tell why she was called Little Tiger.
From watching the video, I could feel her daring spirit.
She has the face of a baby and the heart of a tiger.
When you become crazy about one thing,
you gain formidable strength.
She has always been crazy about edible greens.
- She'll be a big tiger soon. - That's right.
- Thank you. - Nice.
It can't be easy.
She's really cool.
Si Hyeon showed us Little Tiger's unexpected daily life.
We'll root for her so that she can charge forward.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(I Live Alone)
(New Footprints)
(Walking)
(She hurries her steps to go somewhere.)
Where is she going so busily?
She isn't here yet.
(Ja Yeon waits for someone at the apartment's resting area.)
(Looking around)
Hye Won!
(Who is it?)
Hello. Isn't it cold?
What are you making to need this?
- It's a secret. - A secret?
- Thank you. - Is it a Karrot transaction?
It's huge.
Why do you have it at home?
It isn't a Karrot transaction.
There's a group chat room for the residents of the apartment.
People give away free items...
and lend the items...
others need.
The neighbors must be close.
- There's still neighborly love. - Yes.
- The neighbors are friendly. - It's like that in Namyangju.
No way. I'll use them well and bring them back to you.
It's nice to see neighbors do that.
Is your cat doing well?
- My cat adjusted well. - I'm curious.
- Please upload some photos. - Okay.
There's also a group chat room for cat owners.
Gosh!
- A group chat for cat owners. - That's so cute.
- I'll see you later. - Right.
There should be one more.
Hi!
Ha Jin!
(Another neighbor brought a different kitchen utensil.)
It's a child.
Is that child part of the community as well?
- It must be a chore. - His mom must have told him to go.
Thank you!
What are you doing with this?
I'm planning to make something.
I'll make something nice and send it back to you.
That's great to see.
Ta-da! Give this jam to your mom.
(She returns the favor with the jam.)
Thank you for coming out.
Bye!
(Bowing)
(After carrying the warmth of the neighbors in both hands, )
(she returns home with a light heart.)
Bom!
Hey, Bom!
- It's a dog-like cat! - Are you here, Bom?
Isn't that a cat we've never seen before?
- I'm back. - It's a baby cat.
- Bom? - Her name is Bom.
She's the second cat in the house.
I see.
She's a very bright and curious...
dog-like cat.
(Bom, second cat)
- She's so pretty. - She's pretty.
She's still a baby.
I was walking with my friend in December...
and my friend spotted a cat.
I noticed the cat as well, but it started running right toward me.
It was a stray cat.
When I saw it from up close,
there was a wound on its back.
I thought an emergency treatment would be enough,
but I was told surgery was required.
The wound on its back...
was decaying.
After letting it go under surgery,
I went the next day.
The doctor asked me...
if I knew more about the cat.
Apparently, the cat was blind...
and was in pain.
Gosh, that poor cat.
Her eyes look very healthy from afar.
They look fine from here.
It had a visual impairment without an external injury...
and it would be hard to find an owner.
That was why I decided to bring her home to raise her...
and she stayed still in my lap.
That would feel touching.
As if we were destined to meet, we met each other on my birthday.
- Gosh. - On your birthday?
- You two were destined to meet. - You two were destined to meet.
The two cats are getting along with each other.
Chacha was very cautious at the start,
but the two really get along with each other now.
I think it took around two weeks for Chacha to open up to her.
The vet said...
the cat wouldn't have survived through winter...
and be able to see spring come...
if I didn't bring the cat.
I wanted the cat's life...
to be full of spring...
and that was why I named her Bom.
She met a great owner.
But there are no inconveniences for her in everyday life.
Her other sense are very developed...
and she remembers where everything is in the house.
- Really? - She can move around freely.
- She moves with her other senses. - Right.
What about the litter box?
She didn't know how to use the litter box at first.
She just went anywhere.
That was why I kept teaching her.
When she was about to poop, I moved her to the litter box.
I did that for a few days while catching her poop with my hands...
and she got used to it.
- She's fine with it now. - What a relief.
Gosh, are you happy to see me?
Come in.
- She's so cute. - Good job.
I'll pet you after washing my hands.
Chacha!
Mom's here, Chacha.
She's always there.
Do you want to sleep more?
Okay.
(It's hard to see the first daughter's face.)
You got another cat while raising one cat.
Isn't it hard to raise two cats?
Are you used to it now?
Having two cats doesn't make it harder.
My friend that rescued Chacha...
takes care of them whenever I get too busy.
That's a relief.
Bom!
They can't be that long.
She's just like her mother.
Here.
(Is she biting the cat treat with her mouth?)
(Sniffing)
This was a method you came up with to cut her nails.
She goes wild if I don't do that.
(Luring her with the cat treat in her mouth)
(Don't cut my nails.)
(Cat treat!)
She's positioned perfectly as she does it so often.
As she's from Seoul National University,
she smartly came up with the position.
She's biting onto the cat treat and you bring up her school?
I would've never come up with that kind of position.
(Growling)
- She doesn't like it. - She doesn't like it.
She wouldn't like it.
But the cat treat must be good.
She has to have the cat treat, but she's also mad about her nails.
(She starts focusing on the treat while complaining.)
(Growling)
"Growl."
- I'm done. - Since she hates cutting her nails,
I've tried many different methods.
Cat treats work the best.
(Entranced)
She sounds like an evil spirit if I don't give her the treat.
- We're done. - Gosh.
(The sound of an evil spirit?)
- You're so fiery. - Show her an actual evil spirit.
- Did you get mad? - She'll behave right away.
Right away.
We still managed to get it done all at once. What a surprise!
(Feeling proud)
Go down!
(She took care of her nails without much trouble.)
The photo is here, Bom!
Gosh! Look at this!
Bom! This is you and Chacha.
- Did you take it yourself? - Yes.
I love taking photos.
(Oktographer's work is full of cats.)
(She puts the photo into a frame.)
Gosh, it looks so nice.
(Did it come out nicely?)
How cute!
- That's so cute. - That's so cute.
(A standing ovation for herself)
- All right. - I should give that a try.
What? Take a picture of a burger and put it up?
No. Take a picture with Kkotbun.
A burger!
Hey, why are you treating him like a beast?
Why would I put up a picture of a burger?
- Since you love burgers. - Right.
(She gets up with a big plastic sheet.)
(She spreads it out on top of the table.)
What is she doing?
(Picking up)
(She gets things out from the bag.)
She must be getting ready to cook.
(Makgeolli and flour?)
- Makgeolli and flour? - Makgeolli and flour.
Isn't she making jeon to have with the makgeolli?
That sounds nice.
- Right? - Yes.
(The table is full of ingredients and kitchen utensils.)
Since Seollal is approaching,
I wanted to make gifts for the people around me.
I'm planning to make some gaeseong juak.
- Gosh, that was hot for a while. - She will actually make that?
I've always loved gaeseong juak.
I think it has been around 3 to 4 years.
The grain syrup has cinnamon and ginger in it.
It seeps out once you take a bite.
I love that taste.
The glutinous rice is really chewy as well.
Isn't it like a donut?
It's in between a yakgwa and a donut.
I remember seeing that before.
There was definitely a time when that was trending.
- Right. Around two years ago? - I remember...
- hearing that term. - Juak.
- Gaeseong juak. - Gaeseong juak.
Many people gave that as gifts.
Have you tried that before?
I haven't.
- Have you tried that before? - Me?
Why am I the only one who has tried it...
when the Gen MZers haven't?
I've tried it as well.
Gosh!
She's making that at home?
How is that made at home?
It doesn't need that many ingredients.
But it must be hard to make at home.
Right.
I find it fascinating that she thought about making that at home.
(She washes her hands cleanly first.)
(Peeking)
(She picks up the sheet of paper that was on the fridge.)
I got close with the cafe owner who sells gaeseong juak.
I was given the cafe owner's recipe,
so I think things will work out well by just following that recipe.
(Shall I begin now?)
(She boldly squeezes out the rice syrup first.)
(A generous amount)
- There's the cinnamon. - There's the cinnamon.
I love cinnamon and ginger.
I love sujeonggwa as well.
(She slices up a generous amount of ginger as well.)
It's exactly what Ja Yeon likes.
Next.
With things like grain syrup, water, honey,
ginger, and cinnamon,
they get boiled together for around 30 minutes.
(Beeping)
(She sets a timer to 30 minutes so that she won't forget.)
(She grabs the glutinous rice flour.)
(A decent amount of glutinous rice flour...)
(and flour get mixed together.)
Done.
There we go.
I do have a strainer at home,
but it isn't as big as that one.
It was nice to be able to borrow it as I was only going to use it once.
(I'm going to spin around as well.)
- She's so cute. - She's so cute.
She's a baby.
Okay.
(She shakes the makgeolli.)
Around 100ml of makgeolli.
- So makgeolli is used. - I add hot water...
for hot water kneading.
Hot water kneading?
Making a dough with hot water is called hot water kneading.
Is that so?
I think Lee Jung has never seen that word before.
- Totally. - It's like...
she's learning a new language.
Hot water kneading.
I didn't want it to be too mushy. I wanted it to be like fresh cheese.
I wanted it to be squeaky.
(The dough is ready. It's time to shape them.)
(Rolling)
(She is very focused with making the shape.)
(The living room is filled with just the sound of the dough.)
Ja Yeon is always quiet when she does these things.
- Others might turn on music or... - Right.
- Or sing. - Exactly.
- She does sing, though. - Okdel.
Right.
(Okdel sings her heart out while playing the piano.)
I quit singing.
I miss Okdel so much.
(Today, she is quietly focused on cooking.)
(She uses both hands this time.)
(Working hard)
I made around 30 to 40 of them.
Doing that many times was quite tough.
Definitely.
What's that?
This feels like a scene in "Surprise Mystery TV."
(This feels like a scene in "Surprise Mystery TV.")
It turns out not to be flour.
- It's something like bone ash. - Right.
(It's something like bone ash.)
"Why was she rolling that together?"
"However!"
"After her new cat came..."
"False!"
(She works hard to make the dough...)
(for the surprise gift.)
This is the last one.
The last one looks very pretty.
(Round)
(Letting out a breath)
(The dough looks round and smooth.)
- She did a great job. - They look pretty.
(Poking)
A hole is made in the dough.
That helps it get cooked to the inside.
- That must be delicious. - That smells so good.
The dough must be fried next.
(She uses the wok she borrowed from her neighbor.)
(Oh, right!)
What?
If there's water on the dough,
- it can pop up. - Right.
It has to be boiled up to 135°C.
The temperature was really important.
Stop at 135°C.
Oh, gosh!
(As she's about to make them...)
I feel nervous.
- Is this your first attempt? - I felt so nervous. Yes.
Your first attempt.
It looks hard to do for someone who hasn't tried it before.
- It looks hard to make. - Right.
(She carefully places them into the oil.)
(Nervous)
From 100°C to 120°C,
I let them get cooked slowly.
So they aren't fried right away at once.
I was told that doing that ruins their shape.
So the temperature is very important.
It looks fine.
Having these many bubbles means it's going well.
(Flipping)
This one flipped.
Okay. That's perfect.
It's going really well.
Since I'm hungry,
(I should have something while it fries.)
I'll have something simple.
(Scrubbing)
It's an apple.
(She adds an apple into the juicer.)
What is that?
- Yam. - Yam?
Half of it. Just this much.
(She puts in the exact amount she wants.)
Walnuts.
(She heads to her plant shelf.)
(Amazed)
Can you do that as an owner of plants?
Well...
(Chuckling)
(She cuts some of the kale she raised.)
Look at the leaves.
(She washes the kale cleanly.)
(After adding in a lot of healthy ingredients, )
(she turns the power on.)
(It turns into a juice nicely.)
(Pouring out)
- The juice comes out right away. - Right. I love that moment.
(Refreshing)
Gosh, this is so convenient.
(She drinks the natural ingredients as a juice right away.)
(Satisfied)
Since it's a juice,
it's easy to take in fruit and vegetables.
(It's easy to take in fruit and vegetables.)
I've been using the juicer these days...
and it tastes really nice and healthy.
(It tastes really nice and healthy.)
I should try that.
- It must be healthy. - Right.
With burgers?
- Right. - Try having burgers like that.
- Sung Hwan. - "With burgers."
- It will mince everything. - Strain out the meat juice.
(Strain out the meat juice.)
I really want to try the juice from the meat juicer.
- The meat juicer? - The meat juicer?
Gosh.
- Gosh! - Wait!
That's not what I meant!
I want to use the juicer...
with vegetables.
- Just have fruit and vegetables. - Right.
I think it will make me much healthier.
- It will bring down my cholesterol. - Right.
I'm going to try that, no matter what.
- It's really good. - It looks good.
They're finding their colors.
That's going to be a success.
(Peeking)
(Plopping up and down)
- Gosh, she's so cute! - What?
She's doing okay, right?
- That's how she sleeps. - She's doing Pilates.
(Shall I start taking them out now?)
She looks like someone with experience.
It must not be that hard to make at home.
It wasn't that hard.
- Didn't she just make it look easy? - Right.
- She's just good at this. - Right.
(Feeling shy)
They turned out nicely.
(Crunch)
- Check out the sound. - Check out the sound.
It must be really good.
(They were cooked nicely.)
(Picking up)
The grain syrup shouldn't be like that.
Gosh, it shouldn't be like that.
- What has gone wrong? - Has the grain syrup gone wrong?
- Is it too thick? - Can I use this?
(The grain syrup is too thick.)
(Thick)
It should be watery. Why has it become like this?
Well, when the grain syrup...
is scooped up like this, it should drip down.
But it became too thick.
I was wondering what went wrong.
(Let's still give it a try.)
(Mixing)
What's wrong about that?
- But... - It looks fine.
Isn't it fine if it tastes good?
(Rattling)
(Hitting)
That was the sound of a rock.
(She takes a bite of it mixed with the grain syrup.)
(Ja Yeon calls someone.)
Hello?
- Ma'am! - Hi.
I tried making the juak.
Is rice syrup different from grain syrup?
- Yes. - They're different, aren't they?
- They're different? - I see.
I used rice syrup.
Oh, dear.
It's really sticky.
The syrup is way too thick.
It's really thick. Check this out.
They won't move at all.
I ruined it.
I got one thing wrong from the recipe.
It was a really important part.
I had to buy grain syrup, but I bought rice syrup instead.
The key point of gaeseong juak is for the sweet syrup...
to flow inside...
and it must seep out after taking a bite.
- Just like that. - Moist.
But as I used rice syrup...
- It became a candied snack. - Right.
- Right? - It became a candied snack.
Let's just call it the gaeseong candy.
Gaeseong candy.
But the inside... Oh, it didn't seep in.
Right. The syrup didn't seep in.
- But how did it taste? - It tasted nice,
but my favorite part of the juak is the syrup...
- Bursting out? - bursting out after a bite.
But the syrup can't seep in if it's too thick.
Is that why it's called that?
- Juak sounds like "burst." - Really?
Really?
- That's why it's gaeseong juak? - You didn't know?
"Gaeseong juak."
That's not true!
- Oh, that's not true? - I thought it was that.
(That's not true?)
Was I too much like a Gen MZer?
(Was I too much like a Gen MZer?)
"Juak!"
Instead of feeling like juak,
it turned out to be more like tanghulu.
(Hitting)
I did so well with the dough.
It's okay. Just go with that.
It will be okay if they are eaten right away.
Okay.
You did well. You really did.
Okay!
- I'll see you soon. - Okay!
I did so well with their shapes.
I used rice syrup...
- and it became too sticky. - What a bummer.
What a bummer.
(Disappointed)
(She still carefully takes them out so they don't stick.)
They're shaped so nicely.
They're so pretty. They look like the ones that are sold.
They all look the same as well.
Let's at least make them look nice with the toppings.
She's even using a forcing bag.
It's not the exact taste of the juak that I love,
but the dough came out well.
If I make it look nice with the toppings,
wouldn't it be edible?
(Wouldn't it be edible if I add toppings nicely?)
Here you go.
You're adding dried fruit too?
It's salivating.
(Gulping)
It really is pretty.
(Shall I put on strawberry too?)
(Chuckling)
Is it too big?
Will it be okay?
(After adding a huge strawberry...)
All right.
- It looks delicious. - It looks really delicious.
I love desserts.
(Ja Yeon's gaeseong juak is ready.)
(Shall I pack them now?)
(Putting it in)
(Neatly put in per topping)
- It's pretty. - It's really pretty.
It looks like juak sold at a store.
(After tying it neatly with a string)
(The Lunar New Year gift set filled with warmth is ready.)
All done.
Chacha, I'll be right back.
She wouldn't get out of that grandma blanket.
(Chacha is here.)
(Jumping)
Bom, have a good time with her.
(She doesn't forget to say goodbye to Bom as well.)
Okay?
(After saying goodbye to Chacha and Bom, )
(she takes her stuff and leaves.)
(She suddenly starts running.)
She's busy.
I should get there fast...
and practice by myself.
- Practice? - Practice what?
- She must have a gathering. - It looks like... Yes.
Oh, dear.
I feel like I know the way around her neighborhood now.
- This apartment complex. - If you go that way,
there's a basketball court...
- and a laundromat. - You're right.
I'm more familiar with her complex than my neighborhood.
(Where Ja Yeon passionately practiced basketball last time)
(She showed a shot that was close to a stunt.)
(Michael Okdon)
(She hurriedly ran to the basketball court.)
They're not here yet.
All right.
(Table tennis tables can be seen in the familiar court.)
- It's table tennis. - You can play table tennis there?
I got to start playing a sport I could play with others...
instead of basketball.
I'll put Michael Okdon aside for now,
and become Ok Table Tennis.
- Ok Table Tennis. - Ok Table Tennis
It suits her. Ok Table Tennis.
I joined a table tennis club this year.
- Table tennis is fun. - Table tennis is fun.
I also used to...
Those who went to the military have pride...
- in their table tennis skills. - Of course.
I'm the best at table tennis...
- Hyun Moo. - among you.
- I'm the best at table tennis... - Hyun Moo.
- among you. - Table tennis is really fun.
I'm almost like the Great Wall of China.
The Great Wall of China? I'll crush you.
Everyone has pride in their table tennis skills.
You're no match for me.
You can't receive my serves.
- I think I can. - My ball would swing past you...
before you even realize.
Well, I'd throw the ball...
and serve sharply like this.
- My serve goes sideways. - Then I'd take it with a spin.
Then I'd hit it back...
- with a backspin. - Then it'd go out.
(I can't believe this.)
My goodness.
(They're all burning with passion for table tennis.)
(I should hurry and practice.)
(Pulling)
(Installing something on the table tennis table)
This equipment helps you control the ball speed,
and it can also decide...
the direction of the ball when it comes out.
So, with this, you can practice freely.
That's available at your apartment complex?
My senior members contributed money to buy that.
- That machine? - Yes.
(Shall I warm up now?)
(Exhaling)
(Beep)
(Hurrying)
It looks like she's training for the national team.
- Even her attire is perfect. - I agree.
(Hitting)
Ja Yeon, you're practicing a consistent swing.
You need to practice until your body remembers.
(Focused)
Considering how it's been only one month for me,
they said I was pretty good. They're complimenting me a lot.
When I went on a trip with my mom,
there was a table tennis table at the hotel,
so we played together, and it was so much fun.
I thought it'd be nice to learn it and play with my mom.
I promised her I'd hone my skills next time I visit her.
That's why I wanted to learn to play table tennis.
And there happened to be a table tennis club...
at my apartment complex.
I'm the youngest member.
A newbie.
(To keep her promise with her mom, )
(she practices hard even by herself.)
(Staring fiercely)
(The stare of a national team table tennis player)
You really look like you are on the national team.
- Looks like she's from Gaeseong. - Yes, a little.
Gaeseong?
She brought gaeseong juak as a gift for the South Korean players.
(She's perfectly prepared with gaeseong juak too.)
"Try this."
Her hometown food.
(They excitedly tease Ok Table Tennis.)
(Ok Table Tennis focuses without budging.)
She also looks like...
- a table tennis robot. - Yes, a little.
(Teasing again)
Your left arm...
- isn't in a cast, is it? - Seriously, her left arm...
It does look like I'm in a cast.
(Laughing)
- She does have a short arc. - She looks a bit...
- I look a little stiff, right? - You do look...
- a little stiff. - You need a bigger arc.
- I'm not so smooth. - You know your stuff, Jun.
I can tell once I see it.
(You're pretty good.)
- If you bend down a bit more... - Will I get better?
(Fixing)
You're too upright now.
You're too upright now. If you fix that...
- You're the one who's most upright. - No.
When you smash,
it needs to go up from down.
But she's standing too upright.
It needs to look like this.
I want to see him play table tennis.
(Anytime)
I can't do it.
(Grunting)
(Exhausted)
Goodness.
It's about time they came.
Gosh, you need to pick up all the balls too.
How can you pick them all up?
(Dragging)
(I should hurry up and clean up before they come.)
That's really useful. The balls go in right away.
(Collecting balls with a fishing net)
(Opening)
- You're here. - Hello.
Hello.
- Hello. - You're the first one here.
Right. I should practice more to catch up with you, Yeon Ok.
Let's begin by warming up...
- when everyone gets here. - All right.
I'm all warmed up.
The machine was so fast.
I had to run around a lot.
That's trouble. It'll be bad if she improves too fast.
I won't be able to play with her.
(Exemplary member, Ok Table Tennis)
- Hello. - Welcome.
- Welcome. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hey.
Hello.
- There are so many members. - Hello.
In total, there are about 20 members.
- It's a pretty big club. - Yes.
Let's gather...
- Let's warm up. - and warm up before we begin.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Oh, he's the president. - Let's stand in a circle.
All right.
- One, two, three, four. - Two, three, four.
- Five, six, seven, eight. - How cute!
I think you make use of the apartment complex the most...
in the country.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
- Two, two, three, four. - I keep hearing weird groans.
- One more time. - They look like villagers...
from "Animal Crossing."
"Animal Crossing?"
- Two, three, four. - Two, three, four.
There are a few expert players.
The expert members fix our postures...
and train us 1-on-1.
We take turns to receive coaching.
And we'd play a 1-on-1 game with them too.
We'd play in doubles too.
- That's how we play. - The residents have fun...
in a really healthy way.
- Since you're a newbie, - Yes.
I'll teach you some postures.
- Okay. - All right.
Experts need to play...
- with newbies. - That's right.
It needs to be the experts.
Let's give it a go.
One, two.
Make it natural and pretty.
- One, two. - He returns the ball well.
- Your form improved a lot. - Right.
You must've practiced a lot.
(The practice paid off.)
All right. One, two.
One, two, one.
- You're good. - Four.
- She's good! - One.
Are you hitting it this way?
If you compliment me...
She suddenly couldn't hit well because of the compliment.
It's natural.
- I'll train my form now. - All right.
- Next player. - Next player.
(Switching with the next player)
- Two of us are playing? - Yes. Shall we warm up?
- Okay. - All right.
She really looks like a pro.
One. That's good.
- Make it natural. - Everyone seems to be good.
Now that we're warmed up,
shall we play doubles?
- Already? - Doubles?
Let's play doubles.
- Doubles. - Already?
- Doubles. - That'd be nice.
Until then, I'd only received coaching and practiced my forms.
That was my first time playing doubles.
(Joining a doubles game for the first time)
You must've been really nervous.
Who decides where we stand?
We'd play rock-paper-scissors to decide.
From there...
(Someone is coaching Ja Yeon before the game.)
He's an expert.
He'd come sometimes and train us passionately.
(Actually, from the side of the court...)
Good.
He does look like an expert.
He doesn't have a title.
They just call him Advisor.
"He's our advisor." Like this.
The doubles team I was in...
composed of me and Advisor.
The opponent team...
was composed of the president and the vice-president.
Oh, my.
A strong team.
You met a strong team.
Since you don't have experience with doubles games,
- learn the rules as we go. - Okay.
- You'll learn as we play. - Okay.
We take turns playing.
- We have to take turns? - Yes, we hit alternately.
(Newbie Ja Yeon happened to be playing with the experts.)
(I, Ok Ja Yeon, )
You're like an athlete.
(work out quite a lot.)
If I play with full concentration,
- I might be able to beat them. - My gosh.
- We got this. - Sorry?
- One, two, three. Let's do it! - Let's do it!
He's cute. "Let's do it!"
- Let's do this. - I'll do my best.
- Let's do this. - All right.
Among them,
there's another match going on.
It's Advisor versus the president.
Actually, it's a match between the two.
(Who is the real table tennis expert?)
- We'll begin. - We'll begin now.
Let's begin.
- Please go easy on me. - Okay.
- I won't make it hard. - Sir, I'm a newbie.
- All right, newbie. - Exactly.
That kind of ball is hard to receive.
(Hitting a home run from the start)
Home run.
Hit it close to your body.
- Okay. - Again.
(Focusing again)
- That's it. Nicely hit. - Yes!
- That was... - Yes!
(Losing points consecutively in an instant)
You shouldn't smash them all. You need to pass a few over.
She's standing too upright.
That's good.
You need to tilt the racket downward when you block.
- Swing like this. - That's it.
- Lower your body. - Lower it! Lower your body.
Here we go.
- This way. - Nice.
- This way. - That was good.
- Nice! - That was a good one.
(Will her counterattack succeed by lowering her body?)
(Not a chance!)
- He scored with that. - He's playing seriously.
Of course, it's a game. All right.
Is it me?
The president didn't go easy on me.
He really isn't.
He hit back the balls mercilessly.
But then again, it's not fun if he goes too easy on me.
- That's true too. - That's right.
It'd hurt your pride if he goes easy on you.
Yes, I don't want that.
- I should lower my body more. - That's right.
Lower more!
- Go low. Go super low. - Switch places.
- One more time. - I'll smash when the time comes.
- Nice. - Mine!
- The president isn't going easy. - He isn't.
(Her body doesn't cooperate easily.)
When I say lower it, I don't mean this.
- I meant, tilt your racket. - Okay.
(Giggling)
It sounds like his tone slightly changed.
I think he's a bit upset.
"Tilt your racket."
- Great. - Lower it.
- That's it. Lower it. - Nice.
- Here you go! - Lower it.
Get that!
(She gives it another try after learning to lower her racket.)
(They lost the 1st set overwhelmingly.)
- You improved a lot, though. - Did I?
It ended right there.
Thank you.
She's indeed...
(Advisor consoles her nonetheless.)
We'll win the next one. I went too easy on them.
- Lower it. - Lower it.
(I can't be a burden to the team anymore.)
"I'll make sure to win."
"I'll do my best." I told myself that.
This is fun.
- Let's do this. - All right. Hit it.
- Let's do it. - Let's go.
- Lower it and hit it. - Lower it.
Lower it.
- Lower it. - Great.
(She received it.)
- Lower it. - Oh, my.
- Lower it. - Great.
Oh, no. That was too slow.
(I have to hit it again.)
- Lower it. - Nice.
(She hit it back properly again!)
The "lower it" method worked.
(Ja Yeon succeeds in attacking.)
- That was great. - She's totally...
(Feeling proud)
(Ok Table Tennis got the hang of it.)
(Right. This is the fun of sports.)
I look excited.
(Her eyes shone even more brightly when she focused.)
- It's only starting. - Let's do this.
- Let's do it! - Let's go.
- What was that? - Hey!
- Gosh! - Nice!
(Get that!)
The deadly smash.
She just smashed like this.
- Well done. - Good job.
Let's catch up.
(Team Ja Yeon is leading the 2nd set.)
Gosh, a sharp serve.
Good. Pass it back.
Gosh, what's this?
- You received that? - All right.
- Lower it. - Lower it.
- It's 6 to 2. - Mine.
(As Ja Yeon suddenly steps up her game, )
- Good. - Oh, no.
(Team Executives starts to sway.)
- Six to nil. - They're caught up in your pace.
When you receive...
The atmosphere matters a lot in table tennis.
I did quite well in the second set.
(In the end, Team Executives loses points consecutively.)
- That was two points. - Two points?
It's about the flow.
- The flow matters in table tennis. - It's about the flow.
- Nice. - Great.
It's 8 to 5.
(Team Ja Yeon and Advisor: 8, Team Executives: 5)
- We just need to win. - Nice.
- It's 9 to 5. - Gosh.
- Gosh. - I thought she'd miss it.
It's one last point.
It's 10 to 6.
Ten to six? We can catch up now.
- We can catch up. - It should be 1 to 1.
Look. He watches his ball like this.
This will decide the set.
(The last rally begins.)
- Nice. - Hit it.
(Groaning)
- We should hit a bit harder. - It's 2 to 1.
- Well done. - We just need one more set.
(The team that wins the 3rd set wins the match.)
This is quite fun, though.
We should wrap it up for them.
Let's decide the match now.
When I say, "Table tennis,"
- you go, "let's have fun." - Okay.
- Table tennis, let's have fun! - Let's have fun!
Gosh, this is my cup of tea.
- "Table tennis, let's have fun." - "Let's have fun!"
- Gosh, this feels familiar. - It's so cute.
- It's retro. - It's fun.
- Seriously. - He added in a chant.
- Table tennis, let's have fun! - Let's have fun!
- Table tennis, let's have fun. - Let's go, team!
- Let's go! - All right. Great.
(The 3rd set begins.)
Lower it.
Lower it!
That was a good serve.
- Ja Yeon, you're good. - Nice.
- Nice. - Yes!
- Here. - Nice.
- She couldn't receive it. - Yes!
- Once more. - One more time.
(Disappointed)
Lower it.
- Okay. - You should lower it.
He's starting to lose his poker face.
- Here it is. - Because it's the last set.
(It's 0 to 1. We need to catch up.)
- That was a good one. - That's it.
She hit it back.
(Team Executives hits it back with ease?)
Gosh, that was short.
- That was good. - The mood is becoming tense.
You followed that up?
Seriously. That was as good as a pro's.
- Nice. - Lower it.
Nice.
He's really good.
- He's good. - Yes!
That's understandable.
- We have 1 point to go. - We have 1 point to go.
It's a match point.
It's doable.
Advisor covered for me so well,
so we're slowly catching up.
(2 point-gap sounds doable.)
The ball will come this way, so get ready to hit it.
Play calmly.
(Team Ja Yeon loses the match if they don't win it this time.)
- Ja Yeon, attack. - Hit it!
- Attack. - Hit it!
- No! - Hit it!
That's a difficult ball.
- Play calmly. - You're too slow.
No, her arm is long.
Hit it!
(I must get this!)
Gosh, she aimed for that.
- She aimed for it. - Totally.
- Great job. - Great job.
- Sir, I'll get that one day. - In the end...
- Good job. - Good job.
You did really well. That was good.
Considering it was her first time, she was really good.
It was horrible.
Come on. I didn't put it that way.
(They compliment the youngest member as soon as the game ends.)
- The atmosphere is really nice. - Tell me about it.
The atmosphere is really nice. It's therapeutic.
I bet so.
The president...
- resembles my dad a bit. - Great job.
- Great job. - The vice-president...
looks like my aunt, so...
They all feel like family.
She's right.
- Let's go have some tea and talk. - Yes.
- Okay. - Okay.
You improved a lot, though.
Considering how it's been a month only,
- I'm good, right? - Yes.
Let's play again next time. I'll get my revenge.
A revenge match.
(They chat amicably even on the way to the cafe.)
All right.
(They enter the cafe within the apartment complex.)
- Follow me. - All right.
- There's a cafe within the complex? - A cafe within the complex?
- Shall we sit on the inside? - Yes.
(Taking it out)
Everyone, I prepared a small gift...
for the Lunar New Year.
Oh, you're giving it to them now.
Oh, the gaeseong juak.
- Well done. - You treated me so well,
- Gosh. - so I felt grateful.
I did my best to make it, but...
- You made them? - Even if it's not good enough...
Yes.
(Moved)
It's more moving that she handmade them.
It's so nice.
Yes. Please open carefully. It could tip them over.
Tip them over?
What could it be that it could tip over?
- It must be barely standing. - Oh, my!
(Exclaiming)
- You made these yourself? - Is it good?
Yes, I made them today.
- Goodness. - Gosh, it's still standing.
It's still standing.
My gosh. This is amazing.
Gosh, they're all so cute.
- The ladies are really cute. - They're too pretty to eat.
They're too pretty to eat.
- I know. - We need to take a photo of it.
- That's right. - Thank you so much.
You prepared the fruits too?
- It's too pretty to eat. - Thank you.
- It's only visually pleasing. - It must've been hard to make it.
I did my best to make it, but I made a major mistake.
- The grain syrup... - The grain syrup?
I added rice syrup instead.
- So, it's... - Too sticky?
- It's too sticky. - I see. It's sticky.
So it tastes a bit like tanghulu.
Tanghulu? I love tanghulu.
Instead of juak,
- They're so sweet. - it tastes like tanghulu.
- So, is it hard? - I know it's lacking... Yes.
- Let's try it. - That's kumquat.
- Oh, kumquat? - It's kumquat.
I love kumquat.
(The baking paper got stuck.)
He's eating the paper too.
Well, you can have it together.
- He ate it without removing it. - Of course.
Be aware of your teeth.
- That must be why you came late. - Yes.
At least it's pretty.
(Sucking)
It's...
"Gosh, I got a dental implant yesterday."
(Joking)
Be careful.
(Savoring)
It looks like he's struggling.
(The tanghulu enthusiast is savoring the gooeyness.)
(Chewing carefully)
It's delicious.
(It's delicious.)
He can't talk.
After everyone tried a piece,
they packed the rest, saying they'd give it to their family.
Later, they messaged me that their kids loved it.
Because kids' teeth are healthy.
(Fortunately, kids have healthy teeth.)
It's too good to eat.
- There's juice inside. - Yes. It's so good.
Who ordered pepper mint tea?
I did.
It's even better.
- Strawberry latte. - Thank you.
Enjoy.
Everyone, let's drink to our victory.
Oh, the loser.
(Bitter)
- Today... - I'm envious.
Although we lost today...
(Upset)
The advisor...
You even added a topspin.
He crossed a line with a topspin.
I just wanted to show her a new technique.
(It was for training.)
- Since I need to experience it. - It was a promise too.
- Also, - It's too quiet.
Let's practice more...
and enter the Namyangju table tennis competition.
- Let's aim for that. - Really?
They must be really serious about table tennis.
I know.
- It's held... - I should practice more.
- around April or June. - That's soon.
Let's enter the competition with Ja Yeon, our newbie,
and make a uniform too.
(They'll make a uniform too!)
- Let's enter the competition. - They have a backstory.
That sounds fun!
Those entering the competition for the first time...
compete in the Hope Division.
- Hope Division? - Hope Division.
It's called Hope Division because newbies need hope.
- Newbie Division. - Newbies.
The amateur table tennis tournament has divisions from 1 to 9.
And below that is an extra division.
- Hope Division? - For absolute beginners.
That's cute. It's called Hope Division.
Hope Division sounds like fun.
Before entering a big competition,
- we should practice. - We must practice.
- Let's do our best. - Let's do this.
It's so much fun.
I'd only interacted with people around my age.
My family lives far apart too.
It's really nice to spend time...
with people who are like mothers and fathers.
(It's nice to spend time with them.)
I'd never met my neighbors like this.
But after moving here,
I got a feeling...
that I have neighbors and that I'm not alone.
I think it's going to be fun, going forward.
To accomplish meaningful results...
in the spring competition,
I'll train super hard.
- Look forward... - It's going to be fun.
To Ok Table Tennis' improvement.
She's like a national representative.
I really can't wait!
Doesn't it look like a sports movie?
Yes, exactly.
She's totally like a national representative.
We have a new movie, right there.
She started playing simply...
at the apartment complex by chance.
- Then she'd go out there... - She became a national player.
- It's like a movie. - And she'd shed tears.
That's right.
It turns out that the advisor...
lost his tooth after eating juak.
Still, to keep the team spirit,
- he'd say that he lost his tooth... - He'd keep it hidden.
- after the game. - That's the story?
He'd smile, and a tooth would be missing.
"What happened?"
"Actually, I wanted you to focus on the game and not bother you."
- "I kept it hidden." - "Why aren't you smiling, Advisor?"
- That's so... - I think there will be...
- That's so ridiculous. - a twist like that.
What is this, "Shaolin Soccer?"
(Completely devoted his artistic soul to the story)
Ja Yeon, every Wednesday,
we should practice super hard.
I'll book the court from 10pm to 11pm.
Sounds good.
We should practice early in the morning too.
(Bonding Naturally)
(Next story)
(A house in a mess)
(There...)
(lived Moomoo with dirty sexy lips.)
(I'm finally making Moo chewy cookies.)
(Chewy)
(These days, when everyone is crazy about Dubai chewy cookies...)
(Hurry up and make them so we can eat them conveniently.)
(When will Hyun Moo start making Dubai chewy cookies?)
(The fans have been hoping for Moomoo to join the trend.)
(You want Moo chewy cookies?)
(I'll make it with basis.)
(Pistachios peeled one by one)
(Kadayif he made himself)
(As thrilling as a blood sugar spike)
(Surprised)
(Come on.)
(I like everything in excess.)
(It's super big, so it's super delicious.)
(Nothing can stop Moo chewy cookies.)
(In a trance)
(Even the air purifier is responding enthusiastically.)
(A container with a good vibe as well)
(Moo Chewy Cookie)
(Where did he go with Moo chewy cookies?)
(President Moo's after service)
(Where there was an all-time best lineup of customers)
(Grand Rainbow Bazaar)
(They donated without hesitation.)
(The generous customers we're grateful for)
(Today, he's repaying their kindness.)
(After Service Moomoo is on the way.)
(You just need to open the door.)
(And your heart as well.)
(Hugging tight)
(Kissing)
(Of the customers)
(For the customers)
(Passionate Moomoo's after service)
It's Moomoo's special service.
(The Rainbow Club President Does Anything for After Service)